I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
The Miscellany series documents many aspects of Pei’s professional life. The award and honorary degree files document the recognition Pei received for his many achievements from the 1960s to 2014. Most notably, the series documents Pei’s significant awards including the 1979 American Institute of Architects Gold Medal, 1983 Pritzker Architecture Prize, 1986 Medal of Liberty, and his election to l’Académie des beaux-arts, Institut de France. Pei’s appointment calendars and logs date from 1955 to 2012 and provide documentation of his work schedule, including daily appointments, events, and meetings. Extensive files document Pei’s travel for a variety of purposes including meetings with clients, monitoring the status of projects, events, and vacations. Arranged according to month of travel, and later by departure date, the files consist of detailed itineraries, correspondence, and documentation of the projects for which he was traveling. Missing from the series are travel files from 1988. The bulk of photographs accessioned as part of the Pei Papers now reside in the Library’s Print & Photographs Division. The photographs in this series mostly include individual portraits of Pei and portraits of his family. Photographs of buildings designed by Pei can be found in the Publicity File, Projects Completed/Inactive, Projects Proposed, Projects Aborted, and Scrapbooks series. Education files mostly document his undergraduate career and 1940 bachelor’s thesis at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, "Standardized Propaganda Units for War Time and Peace Time China." Notably missing is a copy of Pei’s master’s thesis at Harvard featuring a Shanghai art museum. The Miscellany series is also composed of biographical files, exhibit files, architectural registrations, recommendation letters for colleagues, and a portfolio prepared by Pei Cobb Freed & Partners that provides general information and images of many of their more notable buildings. Very little biographical information exists from Pei’s early life in China before he immigrated to the United States.
The Subject File series includes documentation of organizations and institutions to which Pei belonged including the Committee of 100, Massachusetts Institute of Technology Corporation, National Council on the Arts, National Council on the Humanities, National Endowment for the Arts, National Endowment for the Humanities, and Urban Design Council of the City of New York. These files document Pei’s membership and involvement within each organization, mostly through correspondence and mailings regarding their activities. Files related to the American Institute of Architect task forces on National Urban Policy and West front of the U.S. Capitol primarily contain research and design information. This series also contains files for various architecture juries on which Pei served from 1955 to 2012, including juries for the National Gallery of Canada, the Parliament House of Canberra, and various design contests.
The Digital Files series contains files from digital storage media removed from paper files in the course of processing. The bulk of these are most closely related to the Publicity File series and include photographs, documentaries, videos of interviews and conversations with Pei, and footage from television shows on which Pei appeared. In some cases, videos focus on the construction of specific buildings such as the Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center and Deutsches Historisches Museum. Digital files related to projects mostly include drawings, plans, and surveys, though there are very few of these.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in ten series:
General Correspondence, 1946-2016
Projects Completed/Inactive, 1959-2013
Projects Aborted, 1966-2011
Projects Proposed, 1952-2012
Publicity File, 1946-2012
Scrapbooks, 1944-2006
Miscellany, 1920-2014
Subject File, 1955-2012
Digital Files, 1995-2012
Oversize, 1958-2009
Container List
- General Correspondence, 1946-2016 (Box 1-135)
  Correspondence and related material including memoranda, reports, proposals, agendas, minutes, mail and invitation logs, programs, announcements, press releases, invitations, resumes, brochures, ballots, interviews, plans, maps, photographs, news clippings, and other printed matter largely relating to Pei’s professional associations, activities, and friendships outside his architectural practice. A small amount of interoffice memoranda from Pei’s architectural firm is included. Other topics include his personal and professional connections within the Chinese diaspora. The series has been maintained for the most part as it was created and used by Pei’s staff. Letters from individual correspondents may be filed either under the person’s name or institutional affiliation. The chronological date span of folders is occasionally broader than the year under which they are filed. Separate files containing copies of Pei’s outgoing correspondence are available for many years beginning in 1953. Mail logs date from 1979 to 2010.
  Arranged chronologically by year span or year and alphabetically therein by name of person, organization, or topic.
  - 1946-1955 (Box 1)
    - American Institute of Architects, New York chapter, Civic Design Committee (Box 1)
    - Baker Furniture (Box 1)
    - Building Research Institute, Washington, D.C. (Box 1)
    - Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence, 1953-1955, (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Colleges and universities (Box 1)
      - Carnegie Institute of Technology, Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 1)
      - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 1)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 1)
      - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J. (Box 1)
      - University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 1)
      - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 1)
    - General, 1946-1954, undated, (5 folders) (Box 1)
    - Hamaguchi, Ryuichi (Box 1)
    - Webb & Knapp (Box 1)
      - Interoffice memoranda (Box 1)
      - Zeckendorf, William (Box 1)
  - 1955-1960 (Box 1)
    - "A" general (Box 1)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
      - Membership (Box 1)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 2)
    - Architectural League of New York (Box 2)
    - Architectural Record (Box 2)
    - Architectural registrations, 1954-1957, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Art and sculpture, list of new European (Box 2)
    - "B-C" general, (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence, 1958-1959, (9 folders) (Box 2)
    - Chang, Chao-Kang (Box 2)
    - Chang, Harold (Box 2)
    - "D-F" general, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Federal Housing Administration Advisory Committee (Box 3)
    - Foreign publications (Box 3)
    - "G-H" general, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - "I-M" general, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Art, Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 3)
    - "N" general, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - National Institute for Architectural Education (Box 4)
    - Nesjar, Carl (Box 4)
    - "O" general (Box 4)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corp., Inter-American Architectural Symposium (1959), Toledo, Ohio, and Bogotá, Colombia (Box 4)
    - "P" general (Box 4)
    - Pennsylvania State University, University Park, Pa. (Box 4)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J. (Box 4)
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 4)
    - "R-T" general See also Container OV 30, Scroll, (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - United Housing Foundation (Box 4)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 4)
    - "V-W" general, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Washington University, St. Louis, Mo. (Box 4)
    - Webb & Knapp (Box 4)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 4)
    - Zeckendorf, Marian and William (Box 4)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 4)
    - "A" general (Box 4)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 4)
      - Convention, Philadelphia, Pa. (1961) (Box 4)
      - General (Box 4)
      - New York chapter, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - American Society of Planning Officials (Box 4)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 4)
    - Architectural League of New York (Box 5)
    - Architectural Record (Box 5)
    - L'Architecture d'aujourd'hui (Box 5)
    - "B-C" general, (5 folders) (Box 5)
    - Citizens' Housing and Planning Council of New York (Box 5)
    - Citizens Union of the City of New York (Box 5)
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y. (Box 5)
    - Committee for the Promotion of an International University in America (Box 5)
    - "D-F" general, (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - F. F. Fraternity (Box 5)
    - "G" general, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce (Box 5)
    - "H" general (Box 5)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - "I" general (Box 6)
    - Interoffice memoranda (Box 6)
      - I. M. Pei & Associates (Box 6)
      - Webb & Knapp (Box 6)
    - "J-M" general, (5 folders) (Box 6)
    - Management consultants (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 6)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 6)
    - Motion picture project, "Formosa" (Box 6)
    - "N" general, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Nelson, R. Gretchen, American Institute of Decorators (Box 6)
    - New School for Social Research, New York, N.Y. (Box 6)
    - "O-P" general, (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 6)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J. (Box 6)
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 7)
    - Publication requests (Box 7)
    - "R" general, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Redevelopment promotion (Box 7)
    - Requests for architectural services (Box 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 7)
    - "S" general, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Slayton, William L. (Box 7)
    - Société pour l'étude technique d'amènagements planifiés (Box 7)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 7)
    - "T" general (Box 7)
    - Thank-you letters, Christmas (1960) (Box 7)
    - "U" general (Box 7)
    - United States government (Box 7)
      - Federal Housing Administration, Industry Advisory Committee (Box 7)
      - State Department (Box 7)
      - United States Information Agency (Box 7)
    - University of California, Berkeley, Calif., Institute of Personality Assessment and Research (Box 7)
    - University of Chicago, Chicago, Ill. (Box 7)
    - "V" general (Box 7)
    - Vogue, article on Pei's Katonah, N.Y., house (Box 7)
    - "W" general, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Waccabuc Country Club, Waccabuc, N.Y. (Box 8)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, N.Y. (Box 8)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 8)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 8)
    - "A" general (Box 8)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 8)
      - National office (Box 8)
        - General (Box 8)
        - National Capital Committee, (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - Pan American Congress (1965) Committee (Box 8)
      - New York chapter (Box 8)
        - General (Box 8)
        - Medal of Honor (Box 8)
      - State chapters (Box 8)
    - Architectural and Engineering News (Box 8)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 8)
    - Architectural Record (Box 8)
    - "B" general (Box 8)
    - Bell, John Price (Box 8)
    - "C" general, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Christmas thank-you notes (Box 9)
    - Citizens Union of the City of New York (Box 9)
    - Conferences (Box 9)
    - Consultation services (Box 9)
    - Contributions (Box 9)
    - "D-G" general, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Gerson, Otto (Box 9)
    - Girard, Alexander (Box 9)
    - Green, Cecil H. (Box 9)
    - "H" general (Box 9)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 9)
      - Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research (Box 9)
      - Graduate School of Design, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - "I" general (Box 9)
    - Inland Cement Co., "Architectural Aspects of the Edmonton Civic Centre Plan" seminar, Edmonton, Canada (Box 9)
    - International Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 9)
    - Interoffice memoranda (Box 9)
      - I. M. Pei & Associates (Box 9)
      - Webb & Knapp (Box 9)
    - "J" general (Box 10)
    - Joint Center for Urban Studies of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 10)
    - "K-L" general, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Life Society Design Committee (Box 10)
    - "M" general (Box 10)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Moore, Henry (Box 10)
    - "N" general (Box 10)
    - Nagel, Chester (Box 10)
    - National Academy of Design (Box 10)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 10)
    - "O-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J. (Box 10)
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 10)
    - Publicity (Box 10)
      - Books (Box 10)
      - General (Box 10)
      - Magazines, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - Newspapers (Box 11)
    - "R" general (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 11)
    - "S" general (Box 11)
    - Slayton, William L. (Box 11)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 11)
    - Szeto, Wei (Box 11)
    - "T-U" general, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - United States government (Box 11)
    - "V-W" general, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Waccabuc Country Club, Waccabuc, N.Y. (Box 11)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 11)
    - Zeckendorf, William (Box 11)
  - 1964 (Box 11)
    - "A" general (Box 11)
    - American Council for Nationalities Service (Box 11)
    - American Federation of Arts (Box 11)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 12)
      - National office (Box 12)
        - Committees (Box 12)
        - Convention, St. Louis, Mo. (Box 12)
        - Fellowship election, (2 folders) (Box 12)
        - General (Box 12)
        - Memo newsletter (Box 12)
      - New York chapter (Box 12)
    - American Museum of Natural History, New York, N.Y. (Box 12)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 12)
    - Architectural Record (Box 12)
    - Associate announcements, I. M. Pei & Associates (Box 12)
    - "B" general (Box 12)
    - Bell, John Price (Box 12)
    - "C" general (Box 12)
    - Christmas cards, personal and office, 1961-1964 (Box 12)
    - City Club of New York, New York, N.Y. (Box 12)
    - Cleveland Institute of Art, Cleveland, Ohio (Box 12)
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y. (Box 12)
    - Conferences (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
      - Third Inter-American Foundation for the Arts Symposium, Mexico City, Mexico (Box 12)
    - Corning Glass Works (Box 13)
    - "D-H" general, (5 folders) (Box 13)
    - Hajjar, A. William (Box 13)
    - Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research (Box 13)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 13)
      - General (Box 13)
      - Graduate School of Design (Box 13)
    - "I" general (Box 13)
    - Interoffice memoranda (Box 13)
    - Invitations (Box 13)
    - "J-K" general, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Kipp, Lyman (Box 13)
    - "L" general (Box 13)
    - Lee, Kyu (Box 14)
    - "M" general (Box 14)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 14)
    - Museum of Modern Art, New York, N.Y. (Box 14)
    - "N" general (Box 14)
    - National Academy of Design (Box 14)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 14)
    - New York Civic Center, New York, N.Y. (Box 14)
    - "O-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Price Tower, Bartlesville, Okla. (Box 14)
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 14)
    - Public Housing Administration, Design Seminar, New York, N.Y. (Box 14)
    - Publicity (Box 14)
    - "R-S" general, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 14)
    - "T" general (Box 14)
    - Turano, E. N. (Box 14)
    - "U" general (Box 15)
    - University of Chicago Press, The People's Architects (Box 15)
    - "V-W" general, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Wayne State University, Detroit, Mich. (Box 15)
    - Webb & Knapp (Box 15)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 15)
  - 1965 (Box 15)
    - "A" general, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Alcoa (Box 15)
    - American Federation of Arts, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 15)
      - General (Box 15)
      - New York chapter (Box 15)
      - Urban Design Short Course East, Society Hill case study, Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 15)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 15)
    - "B-C" general, (5 folders) (Box 16)
    - Chen Chi-kwan (Box 16)
    - City Club of New York, New York, N.Y., Albert S. Bard Awards (Box 16)
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y. (Box 16)
    - Conferences (Box 16)
    - "D-E" general, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Eurich, Nell P. (Box 16)
    - "F-G" general, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - General Electric Forum (Box 17)
    - Green, Cecil H. (Box 17)
    - "H" general (Box 17)
    - Harvard Graduate Society for Advanced Study and Research, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 17)
      - General (Box 17)
      - Graduate School of Design (Box 17)
    - Hope, Constance (Box 17)
    - Hotel reservations (Box 17)
    - "I" general (Box 17)
    - I. M. Pei & Associates (Box 17)
      - General (Box 17)
      - Interoffice memoranda (Box 17)
      - Labor hours weekly reports, Aug.-Dec. (Box 17)
    - Invitations (Box 17)
    - "J-K" general, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - "L-M" general, (4 folders) (Box 18)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Motohara, Kazumitsu, handmade book with photographs of watercolor drawings from 1964 world trip (Box 18)
    - "N" general (Box 18)
    - National Academy of Design (Box 18)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - New York City Task Force on Housing and Urban Renewal, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 18, Box 19)
    - New York University, New York, N.Y. (Box 19)
    - "O-P" general, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 19)
    - Publicity (Box 19)
    - "Q-R" general (Box 19)
    - "S" general, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 19)
    - State University of New York, New York, N.Y. (Box 19)
    - "T-U" general, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - United States government (Box 19)
    - "V" general (Box 19)
    - "W" general, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Webb & Knapp (Box 20)
    - Woo, Peter (Box 20)
    - "X-Z" general (Box 20)
  - 1966 (Box 20)
    - "A" general (Box 20)
    - American Federation of Arts (Box 20)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 20)
    - "B-G" general, (6 folders) (Box 20)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth (Box 20)
    - Goals for Dallas conference, Salado, Tex., (3 folders) (Box 20)
    - Graham, Katharine (Box 21)
    - Green, Cecil H. (Box 21)
    - "H" general (Box 21)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 21)
    - I. M. Pei & Partners, announcement (Box 21)
    - "J-N" general, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Nesjar, Carl See also Container OV 45, Photographs (Box 21)
    - "O-P" general (Box 21)
    - Publicity (Box 21)
    - "R" general (Box 21)
    - Regional Plan Association (Box 21)
    - "S" general (Box 21)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 21)
    - "T" general (Box 21)
    - Thursday Morning Talks program (Box 21)
    - "U" general (Box 21)
    - United States government (Box 21)
    - "V-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - 1967 (Box 21)
    - "A-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong, Kowloon, Hong Kong (Box 21)
    - "D" general (Box 21)
    - "E-F" general (Box 22)
    - Ford Foundation, urban design study (Box 22)
    - "G-H" general (Box 22)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 22)
    - "I" general (Box 22)
    - Invitations, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - "J-L" general (Box 22)
    - Lee, Richard C. (Box 22)
    - "M-N" general (Box 22)
    - Nagel, Chester (Box 22)
    - National Citizens' Committee for Public Television (Box 22)
    - National Council on the Humanities, James Lawrence proposal (Box 22)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 22)
    - "O-P" general (Box 22)
    - Publicity (Box 22)
    - "R" general (Box 22)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., proposed memorial, Washington, D.C. (Box 22)
    - "S-T" general, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Texas Society of Architects (Box 23)
    - "U" general (Box 23)
    - United States government, State Department (Box 23)
    - "V-W" general (Box 23)
    - Williamsburg Restoration, Inc. (Box 23)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 23)
  - 1968 (Box 23)
    - "A" general (Box 23)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 23)
    - "B" general (Box 23)
    - Bassett, Florence Knoll (Box 23)
    - Breuer, Marcel (Box 23)
    - "C" general (Box 23)
    - Chinese embassy, Republic of China (Box 23)
    - "D" general (Box 23)
    - Dallas Assembly (Box 23)
    - "E-G" general (Box 23)
    - General Property Corp. (Box 23)
    - Goals for Dallas (Box 23)
    - Goyer, Charles Wesley (Box 24)
    - "H" general (Box 24)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 24)
    - "I-K" general (Box 24)
    - Invitations (Box 24)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 24)
    - "L-P" general, (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J., conference (Box 24)
    - Publicity (Box 24)
    - "R-W" general, (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - WGBH television station, (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Webb & Knapp (Box 25)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 25)
    - Zajac, Jack (Box 25)
    - Zeckendorf, William (Box 25)
  - 1969 (Box 25)
    - "A" general (Box 25)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 25)
      - National office (Box 25)
        - Committee on Institute Headquarters (Box 25)
        - Convention, Chicago, Ill. (Box 25)
        - General (Box 25)
      - New York chapter (Box 25)
    - "B-C" general, (3 folders) (Box 25)
    - Chinese embassy, Republic of China (Box 25)
    - "D-F" general (Box 25)
    - Fuller, R. Buckminster (Box 25)
    - "G-I" general, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 26)
    - Invitations (Box 26)
    - "J-L" general, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Lindsay, John V., campaign, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - "M-O" general, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Oversea-Chinese Banking Corp. (Box 26)
    - Overview Group, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - "P" general (Box 26)
    - Publicity (Box 26)
    - "Q-W" general, (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - WGBH television station, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 27)
  - 1970 (Box 27)
    - "A-B" general, (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Boston, Mass., Chinatown (Box 27)
    - Boston Magazine interview (Box 27)
    - "C" general (Box 27)
    - Committee of One Hundred Architects and Planners for Peace (Box 27)
    - "D-E" general (Box 27)
    - Evolution Steering Committee (Box 27)
    - "F-H" general, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Invitations, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - "J-M" general (Box 28)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 28)
    - Moore, Henry (Box 28)
    - "N-T" general (Box 28)
    - Patiño R., Antenor (Box 28)
    - Publicity (Box 28)
    - "R-S" general (Box 28)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 28)
    - "T-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Zao, Wou-ki (Box 28)
  - 1971 (Box 28)
    - "A" general (Box 28)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 28)
    - "B" general (Box 28)
    - Breuer, Marcel, committee (Box 28)
    - "C-D" general, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Dubuffet, Jean (Box 28)
    - "E-G" general (Box 28)
    - General Property Corp. (Box 28)
    - "H" general (Box 28)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 29)
    - "I" general (Box 29)
    - Invitations (Box 29)
    - "J-M" general (Box 29)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 29)
    - "N-P" general (Box 29)
    - Peng, Y. H. (Box 29)
    - Publicity (Box 29)
    - "R-S" general (Box 29)
    - Salgo, Nicholas M. (Box 29)
    - "T" general (Box 29)
    - Tan Chin Tuan (Box 29)
    - "U-Y" general, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Yang, Yingfeng (Yuyu) (Box 29)
    - Zao, Wou-ki (Box 29)
  - 1972 (Box 29)